GUIDE TO THE AMERICAN ASSOCIATION OF SCHOOL ADMINISTRATORS COLLECTION MS2352
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Governance/ Planning, 1921-2006; Series 3; 26.5 Linear Feet
  - Executive Committee, 1982; 3 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Executive Committee, 1982; 3 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Executive Committee, 1983-1984; 3 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Executive Committee, 1984 February; 3 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Executive Committee, 1984 March; 3 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Executive Committee, 1985; 3 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Executive Committee, 1985 March; 3 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Executive Committee [1/2], 1985 June; 3 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Executive Committee [2/2], 1985 June; 3 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee, 1988 March; 3 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Executive Committee [1/3], 1988; 3 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Executive Committee [2/3], 1988; 3 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee [3/3], 1988; 3 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Executive Committee [1/3], 1989 June; 3 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Executive Committee [2/2], 1989 June; 3 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Executive Committee [3/3], 1989 June; 3 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Executive Committee [1/3], 1989 September; 3 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Executive Committee [2/3], 1989 September; 3 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Executive Committee [3/3], 1989 September; 3 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee [1/2], 1990 February; 3 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Executive Committee [2/2], 1990 February; 3 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Executive Committee [1/4], 1990 April; 3 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Executive Committee [2/4], 1990 April; 3 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Executive Committee [3/4], 1990 April; 3 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee [4/4], 1990 April; 3 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Executive Committee, 1991 September-December; 3 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Executive Committee, 1995 November; 3 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Executive Committee, 1997 September; 3 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Executive Committee [1/2], 1997 November; 3 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Executive Committee [2/2], 1997 November; 3 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Executive Committee, 1998 February; 3 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Executive Committee, 1998 April; 3 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Executive Committee [1/2], 1998 November; 3 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Executive Committee [2/2], 1998 November; 3 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Executive Committee, 2001 Novemver; 3 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Executive Committee [1/2], 2002 May; Series 3 (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - Executive Committee [2/2], 2002 May; Series 3 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Executive Commitee Agenda, February, 1992; Series 3 (Box 316, Folder 5)
  - Executive Committee for Consideration at Next Meeting, 1984-1988; 3 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Executive Committee Correspondence [1/2], 1962-1963; Series 3 (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - Executive Committee Correspondence [2/2], 1962-1963; Series 3 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Executive Committee Flash Report, 1991 November; 3 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Executive Committee Leadership Conference, 2003 April; 3 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1969; 3 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1979 June; 3 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee Meeting and Agenda, 1980-1981; 3 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1981 June; 3 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1983; 3 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1988 January; 3 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1988 January; 3 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Executive Committee Meeting [1/2], 1988 June; 3 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Executive Committee Meeting [2/2], 1988 June; 3 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Executive Committee Meeting [1/3], 1989 March; 3 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Executive Committee Meeting [2/3], 1989 March; 3 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee Meeting [3/3], 1989 March; 3 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Executive Committee Meeting Agendas, 1990; 3 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Executive Committee Meeting and Minutes [1/2], 1984; 3 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Executive Committee Meeting and Minutes [2/2], 1984; 3 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Executive Committee Meeting [1/2], 1984 November; 3 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Executive Committee Meeting [2/2], 1984 November; 3 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1991 February; 3 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Executive Committee Meeting [1/2], 1997 April; 3 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Executive Committee Meeting [2/2], 1997 April; 3 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Executive Committee Meeting [1/2], 1998; 3 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Executive Committee Meeting [2/2], 1998; 3 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee Meeting [1/2], 1998 May; 3 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Executive Committee Meeting [2/2], 1998 May; 3 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Executive Committee Meeting [1/2], 1998 September; 3 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Executive Committee Meeting [2/2], 1998 September; 3 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee Meeting [1/3], 2004 October; Series 3 (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Executive Committee Meeting [2/3], 2004 October; Series 3 (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - Executive Committee Meeting [3/3], 2004 October; Series 3 (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Executive Committee Meeting Binder, 2004 April; Series 3 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1921-1929; 3 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Executive Committee Minutes [1/2], 1930-1939; 3 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Executive Committee Minutes [2/2], 1930-1939; 3 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee Minutes [1/2], 1940-1949; 3 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Executive Committee Minutes [2/2], 1940-1949; 3 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Executive Committee Minutes [1/2], 1950-1955; 3 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Executive Committee Minutes [2/2], 1950-1955; 3 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1951-1955; 3 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1956-1958; 3 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Executive Committee Minutes [1/2], 1956-1959; 3 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee Minutes [2/2], 1956-1959; 3 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1957-1958; 3 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1959-1961; 3 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1960-1961; 3 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Executive Committee Minutes [1/2], 1962; 3 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Executive Committee Minutes [2/2], 1962; 3 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1963; 3 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1963-1964; 3 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1964; 3 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1964-1965; 3 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1965; 3 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1965-1966; 3 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Executive Committee Minutes [1/2], 1966-1967; 3 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Executive Committee Minutes [2/2], 1966-1967; 3 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1967; 3 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Executive Committee Minutes [1/2], 1968; 3 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Executive Committee Minutes [2/2], 1968; 3 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1969; 3 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Executive Committee Minutes [1/2], 1970; 3 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Executive Committee Minutes [2/2], 1970; 3 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1971; 3 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1971-1972; 3 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1972-1973; 3 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Executive Committee Minutes [1/2], 1972-1973; 3 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Executive Committee Minutes [2/2], 1972-1973; 3 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1973-1974; 3 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Executive Committee Minutes [1/2], 1973-1974; 3 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Executive Committee Minutes [2/2], 1973-1974; 3 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1974-1975; 3 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1976; 3 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1975; 3 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1976; 3 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1977; 3 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1977; 3 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee Minutes [1/2], 1978-1979; 3 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Executive Committee Minutes [2/2], 1978-1979; 3 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1978; 3 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1979; 3 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1980; 3 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1980-1982; 3 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Executive Committee Minutes [1/3], 1981-1984; 3 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Executive Committee Minutes [2/3], 1981-1984; 3 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Executive Committee Minutes [3/3], 1981-1984; 3 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1987; 3 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1988; 3 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1989 March; 3 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1989 March; 3 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1990; 3 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1990 February; 3 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1991; 3 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, February 19, 1992 (Box 316, Folder 6)
  - Executive Committee Minutes [1/2], 1992-1993; 3 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Executive Committee Minutes [2/2], 1992-1993; 3 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1993 February; 3 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1993 September-1994 March; 3 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1994-1995; 3 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1994 April-1995 February; 3 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1994 November-1995 November; 3 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1995 April-1996 November; 3 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1995-1996; 3 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1996 September- 1997 September; 3 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1997; 3 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1997 September - 1998 November; 3 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1999 February-1999 November; 3 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1999 November-2000 November; 3 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Executive Committee Orientation Handbook [1/2], 2001; Series 3 (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Executive Committee Orientation Handbook [2/2], 2001; Series 3 (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Executive Committee Reports, 1977-1980; 3 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Evaluation of Dr. Richard Miller, Executive Director AASA, 1990 Novemver; 3 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Exhibits History [1/4], 1968-1984; 3 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Exhibits History [2/4], 1968-1984; 3 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Exhibitions History [3/4], 1968-1984; 3 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Exhibitions History [4/4], 1968-1984; 3 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Family Education Network [1/2], 1996-2000; 3 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Family Education Network [2/2], 1996-2000; 3 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Family Education Network, 1997; 3 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Financial History: Contracts & Audits [1/6], 1987-2001; 3 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Financial History: Contracts & Audits [2/6], 1987-2001; 3 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Financial History: Contracts & Audits [3/6], 1987-2001; 3 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Financial History: Contracts & Audits [4/6], 1987-2001; 3 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Financial History: Contracts & Audits [5/6], 1987-2001; 3 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Financial History: Contracts & Audits [6/6], 1987-2001; 3 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Financial Incentives For Attracting and Keeping Administrative Talent; A Brief Summary, undated; Series 3 (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Florida Assoc of DA, 2004 September; 3 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Focus on Math, undated; 3 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Ford Foundation, 1976-1982; 3 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Fordham University, 2003 July; 3 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Forest T. Jones (And TIE) [1/4], 1978-1996; 3 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Forest T. Jones (And TIE) [2/4], 1978-1996 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Forrest T. Jones (And TIE) [3/4], 1978-1996; 3 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Forrest T. Jones (And TIE) [4/4], 1978-1996; 3 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Frank Yulo Memorial Service, 2003 March; 3 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - FY05 Program Plan, 2004 April; Series 3 (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - Georgia ASA, 2001 October; 3 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Georgia ASA Institute, 2003 June; 3 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Georgia Leadership Academy, 2001 November; 3 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Governing Board Meeting, 2004 February; Series 3 (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - Harvard Advisory Panel, 2001 October; 3 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Harvard Summer Seminar, 2000 July; 3 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Harvard Summer, 2003 July; 3 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Harvard Urban Supts Advisory Panel, 2002 October; 3 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Harvard Urban Supts Advisory Panel, 2003 October; 3 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Harvard Urban Supts Advisory Panel, 2004 October; 3 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Hechinger Institute, 2002 March; 3 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - Hope Foundation, 2001 November; 3 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Hope Foundation, 2002 April; 3 (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - Hope Foundation, 2002 October; 3 (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - Hope Foundation, 2002 November; 3 (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - How Our Investment in Education Pays Off, undated; 3 (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - IEI- John Goodlad, 2004 August; 3 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Illinois ASA, 2002 May; 3 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Indiana Assoc Fall Conf, 2003 September; 3 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Indianapolis Public Schools, 2002 August; 3 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Investing In Education, 2001 January; 3 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Investing In Socially Responsible Education, 2004; 3 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Joe Cirasuolo Retirement, 2002 October; 3 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Josephson Institute, 2004 October; 3 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - John Goodlad, 2003 May; 3 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Joint Committee, National School Board Association and AASA, 1962; Series 3 (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Joint Committee [loose documents] National School Board Association/ AASA, 1968-1969; Series 3 (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Joint Committee [loose documents] National School Board Association/ AASA, 1971-1973; Series 3 (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Joint Committee [loose documents] National School Board Association/ AASA, 1974; Series 3 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Joint Committee [loose documents] National School Board Association/ AASA, 1975; Series 3 (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Joint Committee [loose documents] National School Board Association/ AASA, 1976; Series 3 (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Joint Committee [loose documents] National School Board Association/ AASA, 1977; Series 3 (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - Joint Committee [loose documents] National School Board Association/ AASA, 1978; Series 3 (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - Joint Committee [loose documents] National School Board Association/ AASA, 1979; Series 3 (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - Joint Committee [loose documents] National School Board Association/ AASA, 1980; Series 3 (Box 94, Folder 10)
  - Joint Committee [loose documents] National School Board Association/ AASA, 1981; Series 3 (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - Joint Committee [loose documents] National School Board Association/ AASA, 1982; Series 3 (Box 94, Folder 12)
  - Joint Committee [loose documents] National School Board Association/ AASA, 1983; Series 3 (Box 94, Folder 13)
  - Joint Committee [loose documents] National School Board Association/ AASA, 1984-1985; Series 3 (Box 94, Folder 14)
  - Joint Committee [loose documents] National School Board Association/ AASA, 1986; Series 3 (Box 94, Folder 15)
  - Joint Committee [loose documents] National School Board Association/ AASA, 1987; Series 3 (Box 94, Folder 16)
  - Joint Committee [loose documents] National School Board Association/ AASA, 1994-1996; Series 3 (Box 94, Folder 17)
  - Joint Committee [loose documents] National School Board Association/ AASA, 1995; Series 3 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Joint Committee [loose documents] National School Board Association/ AASA, 1996; Series 3 (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - Joint Committee [loose documents] National School Board Association/ AASA, undated; Series 3 (Box 93, Folder 9)
  - Jordan School District, 2003 August; 3 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - J. Paul Getty-Nation At Risk, 2003 October; 3 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - July Executive Comm/ Summer Inst, 2004 July; 3 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Large City Schools Superintendents Conference Houston, Texas, 2001 January; 3 (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Large City Schools Superintendents' Conference, 2002 January; 3 (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - Large City School Superintendents Annual Conference, 2003 January; 3 (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - LCSS Conference, 2004 January; 3 (Box 66, Folder 16)
  - LSCSS Summer Conference, 2004 June; 3 (Box 66, Folder 17)
  - Large City School Superintendents (LCSS), 2005 June; 3 (Box 66, Folder 18)
  - Leadership Conference, 2001 May; 3 (Box 66, Folder 19)
  - Learning First Alliance, 2001 January; 3 (Box 66, Folder 20)
  - Learning Laboratories Initiative, Building the Future, 1991 March; 3 (Box 66, Folder 21)
  - Louisiana Assoc of School Executives, 2002 November; 3 (Box 66, Folder 22)
  - Market Research Survey, 1992 April; 3 (Box 66, Folder 23)
  - Massachusetts Mid-Winter Conference, 2003 January; 3 (Box 66, Folder 24)
  - Memorandum 87-29, 1987; 3 (Box 66, Folder 25)
  - Memorandum, 1992; 3 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Memorandum, undated; 3 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Memorandum and Executive Committee, 1982; 3 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Michigan Association of School Admin (ASA), 2002 January; 3 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Minnesota ASA, 2001 September; 3 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Minnesota ASA Board Directors, 2005 June; 3 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Minutes Of The ASA Executive Committee, 1985; 3 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Minutes Of The AASA Executive Committee, 1986; 3 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Minutes of Executive Committee Meeting, 1991 September; 3 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Mission, Goals, Platform, Resolutions, and Legislative Agenda, 1990-1994; Series 3 (Box 252, Folder 8)
  - Mission, Platform, Resolutions and Legislative Agenda, 1994; 3 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Montana Conference On Education Leadership, 2002 October; 3 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - National Academy For Superintendents, 2001 July; 3 (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - National Board For Professional Teaching Standards Report, 1991 December; 3 (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - National Board For Professional Teaching Standards Report, 1991 December; 3 (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - National Conference on Education Binder, 2006 February; Series 3 (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - National School Boards Association [loose documents], 1964-1965; Series 3 (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Nat'l Forum On Ed Policy, 2005 July; 3 (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - National School Boards Association (NSBA), 2001 March; 3 (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - National School Boards Foundation/ NSBA, 2002 April; 3 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - National School Change Awards, 2005 July; 3 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - National Supt Academy, 2003 June; 3 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - National Study of School Evaluation (NSSE) Board Meeting, 2002 July; 3 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - National Summit On Recruiting, Retaining, and Certifying Quality Teachers, 2003 Apirl; 3 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - National Superintendent Of The Year Recognition Program, 1992; 3 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Nebraska Admin Conf, 2003 July; 3 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Negotiated Rulemaking, 1982-1989; Series 3 (Box 253, Folder 1)
  - Nevada ASA Spring Conf, 2003 June; 3 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - New England School DEV: Sturbridge, CT Council, 2001 May; 3 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - New Jersey Title I Leadership DEV Inst, 2002 August; 3 (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - New Mexico ASA, 2003 July; 3 (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - New Priorities, A Survey Of The National Mood, 1992; 3 (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - New Priorities: A Survey Of The National Mood, 1992; 3 (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - New Orleans, 2002; 3 (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - New Schools Meeting, 2001 October; 3 (Box 68, Folder 15)
  - New Clipping: Stopping The Violence, 1992 November; 3 (Box 68, Folder 16)
  - North Central Association Coll/Schools, 2002 April; 3 (Box 68, Folder 17)
  - November Executive Committee, 2002 November; 3 (Box 68, Folder 18)
  - November Exec Committee, 2003 November; 3 (Box 68, Folder 19)
  - NSBA Annual Conference, 2003 April; 3 (Box 68, Folder 20)
  - NSBA Conference, 2004 March; 3 (Box 68, Folder 21)
  - NSBA Annual Conf, 2005 April; 3 (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - NSSE Board Meeting, 2000 July; 3 (Box 68, Folder 23)
  - NSSE, 2001 July; 3 (Box 68, Folder 24)
  - October Executive Committee, 2004 October; 3 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - October Executive Committee, 2005 October; 3 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Ohio State University, 2005 April; 3 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Opinions And Status Of AASA Members, 1982; 3 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Oklahoma Women Admin Conference, 2002 December; 3 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Parents...Partners In Education, 1982; 3 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Partnerships Connecting School And Community, undated; 3 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Past Presidents Conference, 2002 June; 3 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Past Presidents Conference, 2003 June; 3 (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Past Presidents/Governance Meeting, 2005 July; 3 (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Pearson Educational Council, 2004 October; 3 (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - Plato Learning Educational Conference, 2005 March; 3 (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - Portland State University, 2005 March; 3 (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - Principals Academy, 2004 June; 3 (Box 69, Folder 14)
  - Principals Academy, 2005 June; 3 (Box 69, Folder 15)
  - Public School Awareness Church Committee Workbook Manual, 1990; 3 (Box 69, Folder 16)
  - Public Tv-Channel 13, 2004 May; 3 (Box 69, Folder 17)
  - Pat Foley Executive Committee Meeting [1/3], 1988 November; 3 (Box 69, Folder 18)
  - Pat Foley Executive Committee Meeting [2/3], 1988 November; 3 (Box 69, Folder 19)
  - Pat Foley Executive Committee Meeting [3/3], 1988 November; 3 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Pat Foley Executive Committee Meeting [1/2], 1989 May; 3 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Pat Foley Executive Committee Meeting [2/2], 1989 May; 3 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Pat Foley Executive Committee Meeting [1/3], 1989 November; 3 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Pat Foley Executive Committee Meeting [2/3], 1989 November; 3 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Pat Foley Executive Committee Meeting [3/3], 1989 November; 3 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Pat Foley Executive Committee Agenda [1/2], 1990 March; 3 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Pat Foley Executive Committee Agenda [2/2], 1990 March; 3 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Pat Foley Executive Committee Agenda [1/2], 1990 June; 3 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Pat Foley Executive Committee Agenda [2/2], 1990 June; 3 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Pat Foley Executive Committee Meeting [1/4], 1990 September; 3 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Pat Foley Executive Committee Meeting [2/4], 1990 Septemer; 3 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Pat Foley Executive Committee Meeting [3/4], 1990 September; 3 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Pat Foley Executive Committee Meeting [4/4], 1990 September; 3 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Pat Foley Executive Committee Meeting [1/4], 1990 November; 3 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Pat Foley Executive Committee Meeting [2/4], 1990 November; 3 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Pat Foley Executive Committee Meeting [3/4], 1990 November; 3 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Pat Foley Executive Committee Meeting [4/4], 1990 November; 3 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Pat F. Executive Committee Meeting [1/4], 1991 February; 3 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Pat F. Executive Committee Meeting [2/4], 1991 February; 3 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Pat F. Foley Lane Executive Committee Meeting [3/4], 1991 February; 3 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Pat F. Foley Lane Executive Committee Meeting [4/4], 1991 February; 3 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Pat F. Foley Lane Executive Committee Meeting [1/3], 1991 March; 3 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Pat F. Foley Lane Executive Committee Meeting [2/3], 1991 March; 3 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Pat F. Foley Lane Executive Committee Meeting [3/3], 1991 March; 3 (Box 73, Folder 5)